uberphones.com 2011-05-08

# Privacy Policy - Uberphones

**Uberphones.com Privacy Statement**

This statement covers the site www.Uberphones.com (“Uberphones”). Please read this statement carefully before using proceeding to access Uberphones. Your use of Uberphones indicates your agreement to abide by the Terms in effect.

**Information Collection**

Uberphones is the sole owner of the information collected on www.Uberphones.com. Uberphones may collect information from our users at several different points on our Web site.

**Mailing List**

Uberphones may launch a mailing list in 2005. In order to sign up to receive regular emails from this mailing list, users must submit information including a valid email address and demographic information such as location and interests. This information will be used in aggregate form only in order to assess general user interest in various internal and third party products and services, and your personal and contact information will not be passed to any other organization. Users who choose to sign up for the mailing list will receive regular emails from Uberphones including new articles added to the site as well as emails from third party Uberphones site sponsors. If you do not wish to receive emails from third party advertisers, do not sign up for the mailing list.

**Third Party Cookies**

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, Uberphones has no access to or control over these cookies, once we have given permission for them to set cookies for advertising. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by Uberphones only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Third Party Advertising**

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by Google, among other services. Information about users’ visit to this site, such as number of times they have viewed an ad (but not username, date of birth, or any other personal information), is used to serve ads to users on this site. For more information about Google and cookies, please click here.

**Log Files**

Like most standard Web site servers we use log files. This includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, platform type, date/time stamp, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement in the aggregate, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses, etc. are not linked to personally identifiable information. We may use a tracking utility that uses log files to analyze user movement.

**Legal Disclaimer**

Though we make every effort to preserve user privacy, Uberphones may need to disclose personal information when required by law wherein we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with a current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on our Web site.

**Business Transitions**

In the event Uberphones goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of its assets, users’ personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

**Links**

The Uberphones web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we, Uberphones, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by Uberphones.

**Third Party Advertising**  
We use MaxOnline and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please [click here](http://www.maxonline.com/privacy_policy/index.php).

**Third Party Cookies**  
In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique â€œcookieâ€ on your browser.

**Notification of Changes**

Whenever Uberphones changes our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, and other places we deem appropriate so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

**Contact Information**

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at contact@Uberphones.com

Link | [Add a Comment](http://www.uberphones.com/2006/01/privacy-policy/#comments)
